Hello.
どうもこんにちは
how are you?
元気ですか?
How are you today?
今日元気?
Yeah.
うん
You're always fine.
いつも元気だね
Yeah.
うん
About 2 months ago?
2ヶ月ぶりぐらい?
yes.
そう
I agree.
そうですね
At the pasta shop, it just so happens that they have the pasta that the prefecture sells.
パスタ屋さんでね、たまたま、県が売ってるパスタあるじゃない
Is it?
ですか
Like a vending machine.
自 販機みたいな
As it happened, we ended up giving each other a little back and forth.
そこでたまたま、ちょっと譲り合いがお互い続いて
copper?
どう?
We got to know each other a little bit there and became good friends.
ちょっとなんか、そこで絡んで仲良くなったんですけど
Do you remember?
覚えてます?
I remember.
覚えてる
It's nostalgic.
懐かしいですね
It's been about 2 months since then.
2ヶ月ぐらい経ってるよ、そこから
I never thought we would end up eating pasta together from there.
まさかね、あそこから一緒にパスタ食うことになると思わなかった
But I'm a little confused.
んだ けど、 俺がちょっと結構、
I didn't force myself, but I told her what to do.
無理やりじゃないけど、 どうすかどうすかって言って
You came alone.
一人で来てたじゃん
Yeah.
うん
I was alone too.
俺も一人だったんで
We talked for a while there and we became friends.
ちょっとそこでね、話しして、仲良くなっちゃったんですけど
Did you actually hate it?
実際嫌だった?
I hated it.
嫌だった
Did you not like it?
嫌だったの?
Did you hate it?
嫌だった?
I actually called out to you at that time, but I didn't like it at all.
実際あの時声かけちゃったけど、ちょっと嫌だったっすか?
I don't dislike it.
嫌じゃない
Didn't you hate it?
嫌じゃなかった?
Yeah.
うん
Is it true?
本当っすか?
good?
よかった?
No, but I never expected it to develop this far since then.
いやでも、まさかあれからここまで発展して、
I'm going to take some naughty pictures today,
今日ちょっとエッチ撮るんですけど、
May I?
いいですか?
Can we have some intense sex?
ちょっと激しいエッチしていいっすか?
Yeah.
うん
So, do you want to take a mask?
じゃあちょっとマスク撮りますか?
It's cute.
可愛いっすね
You have a nice smile.
笑顔がいいっすね
It's different from last time, isn't it?
なんかでもこの前と違うっすね
What's the difference?
何が違いますか?
Did you change anything?
何か変えた?
I haven't changed it.
変えてない
Haven't you changed it?
変えてない?
hairstyle.
髪型
Your hairstyle has changed.
髪型変わったね
Has it changed?
変わった?
Yes, when we first met.
そう、初めて会った時
That's right.
そうだよね
I haven't changed it.
変 えてないって
What kind of hair was it?
どんな髪だった?
No, I don't really remember much.
いや、ちょっとあんま覚えてないな
So, can I have you come around a little bit?
じゃあちょっとくるって回ってもらっていい?
OK、
Shall I take it off?
脱 ぎましょうか
Well, you can remove the top a little.
じゃあ上ちょっと抜いていいよ
Yes.
はーい
Bra, no bra?
ブラ、ブラない?
do not have.
ない
Isn't it a brush?
ブラシじゃないの?
do not have.
ない
picture?
え?
That's amazing.
すごいね
Your breasts are so beautiful.
おっぱいめっちゃ綺麗だね
Aren't your breasts so beautiful?
おっぱいめっちゃ綺麗じゃないですか
It looks like it's still going to get bigger.
まだ大きくなりそうだね
These boobs look like they're still going to get bigger.
このおっぱいはまだ大きくなりそうだね
Still growing?
まだ成長中?
Isn't it growing?
成長中じゃない?
Just take off your pants.
ちょっとズボンを脱いで
I like those pants.
いいね、そのパンツ
Can I take a guess at this?
ちょっとこれ当てていい?
Can I touch your neck for a moment?
ちょっとこっち首当てていい?
amazing.
すごい
How far?
どこまで?
Oh, you can show me your pussy.
お、マコ見せていいよ
Well, I'll guess this next time.
じゃあ次これ当てていくね
Shall I come in?
入るか
I think I'll put it in.
入れそう
I'll put this in.
入れちゃうよ、これ
Ah, it's in.
あー、入ったな
Then this one is next.
じゃあ次こいつね
Now, open it up.
さあ、おまく開いて
I'll open it myself, over here.
自分で開けるよ、こっちこっち
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Well then, the most
じゃあ、 最
For the first time, from the state where the penis is covered.
初 チンチン被ってる状態から
Lick it.
舐めて
Finally, get it all wet and put it in your pussy.
最後いっぱい濡らして、おまんこ入れよ
Yeah, probably.
うん、多分
Shall I put it in?
入れよっか
Get your hands on me and stab me.
手立ててさ、抜き刺して
Wait a minute, then.
ちょっと、そしたら
I'll put it in.
入れるよ
degree
ど
Can I take this out?
こ 出していい?
Can I cum inside you?
中出しちゃいい?
Let's go.
いくよ
Where can I take it out?
ど こ出していい?
Can I cum inside you?
中出しちゃいい?
Let's go.
いくよ
How was your day?
どうでしたか、今日は?
It felt good.
気持ちよかったです
Did it feel good?
気 持ちよかったですか?
So let's do it again next time.
じゃあまた今度やりましょうね
Well, for the last time, bye-bye.
じゃあ最後、バイバイで
bye bye.
バイバイ